A Guide to the Paul A. Weiss papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA124
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1940-1976; 4; 0.88 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes articles, notes, photographs, correspondence and ephemeral material on topics, lectures, symposiums and news items.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by topic.
  - Biomathematics (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Developmental Biology (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Environment (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Environment (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Environment (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Environment (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Environment (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Biology (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Federal Research Support and US Education (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Humanism and Humanities (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Science Policies (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Systems (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - World Directory of Physiologists, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Lectures, 1946-1972; 5; 7.92 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes notes, lecture outlines, photographs, news clippings and correspondence.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by lecture topic and/or location.
  - Airlie House (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Alabama College (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Albany Medical College (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - American Association of Plastic Surgery (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - American Cancer Society (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - American Chemical Society Symposium, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - American Society for Cell Biology (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - American Society for Surgery of the Hand, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - American Society of Plastic and Reconstructive Surgery, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Amherst Lecture, 1961 June (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 1 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 2 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    Scope and Contents
    The collection does not contain a "Lecture 3".
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 4 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 5 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 6 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 7 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 8 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 9 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 10 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 11 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 12 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 13 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 14 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Analysis of Development Lecture 15 (*there was no Lecture 3 found) (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Arches of Science Award (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Arden House, 1961 March (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Arkansas, 1977 March (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Arthritis and Rheumatism Foundation (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Course Syllabi (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Atlantic City, 1975 April (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Augusta, Georgia (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Austin, Texas, 1965 October (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - A Basic Predecessor of Applied Heart Transplantation (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Baylor University, 1964 November (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Berkeley, 1963 April (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Bielefeld Lecture, 1971 May (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Biology and Behavior (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Biology of the Skin (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - BBC Lecture, 1966 May (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Brevard College (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Bucknell Students' Seminar, 1962 February (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Brooklyn Polytechnic Institute (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Boston College, 1963 April (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Brown University, 1974 April (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo, New York, Spring 1967 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Can Science Help to Thing the Fog.... (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Cancer (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Cancer as View by the Biologist (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Cancer Research Conference, 1962 June (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Catholic University of America (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Cell and Cell System Ecology (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Cell Interaction with Surfaces (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - A Cell is not an Island (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Cell Locomotion (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Cell Surface and Cancer (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Cell Symposium (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Cellular Growth (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Centennial Symposium on Brain Research (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Center for Human Understanding (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Chemical Organization of Cells (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Chester Beatty Research Institute (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Chicago Holiday Lecture, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Christmas Lectures, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Christmas Lectures, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Clark University, 1974 May (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland College, 1960 November (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Cleveland Trip, 1973 March (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Cognate Lecture, 1965 October (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - College de France (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Colloquium at City College (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Columbia Cell Biology Seminar (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Teachers College (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Conference on Cellular Dynamics, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Cellular Dynamics, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Central Nervous Systems (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Conference on Marine Biology (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Conference on Renewable Resources (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Congress on Medical Education (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Conference on Organogenesis (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Cooperative Forum (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Coordination of Federal Science Activities (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1955-1956 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1961-1963 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Declined Lecture Invitations, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Depolarization (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Depolarization of Conflict (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Development of Structure (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Developmental Biology (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Differentiation and Development Symposium (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Differentiation and Its Three Facets (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Downstate Medical Center (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Dynamics and Mechanics of Neuroplasmic Flow (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Dynamics of Degeneration and Growth in Neurons (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Eastern Surgical Society (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Eighth International Embryological Conference, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Emperische Grundlagen des Systemdenkens (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Engineering Study of the Peristaltic Drive of Axonal Flow (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Ethicon, Inc. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Experimentally Enforced Axonal Flow (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Fourth International Neurochemical Symposium (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Frankfurt, 1970 October (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Frankfurt, 1971 May (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Fridley Lectures, 1962 November (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - From Cell Research to Nerve Repair (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Fundamentals of Systems Causality in Nature (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Fundamentals of Systems Causality in Nature (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Galveston, 1966 January (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Gastroenterologists (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Gaylor Hospital, 1963 April (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Graham Foundation (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Gordon Conference, 1963 August (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Gordon Conference, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Gottingen, 1975 November (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Gould House of Science Writers (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Group Patterns of Cell Organelles (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Hagerstown Workshop (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Hahnemann Medical College (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Medical Development Conference (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Medical School (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University Biological Laboratories (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Harvey Cushing Society (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Society Lecture, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Heidelberg, 1974 June (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - H. H. Whitney Foundation Tissue Conference (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Hellenic Society Symposium, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Hellenic Society Symposium, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Hellenic Society Symposium, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Helsinki, 1966 September (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Henry Ford Hospital Symposium, 1961 May (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Henry Ford Hospital Symposium, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - High School Biology Teachers (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Higher Education for Science and Technology (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Hohere Erziehung fur Wissenschaft..... (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Holiday Lecture, 1962-1963 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Holiday Lecture, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Lecture (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Hospital for Special Surgery (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Houston Baptist College (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Houston Philosophical Society (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Humanities Conference (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hungary, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Indiana Lectures, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - International Biophysics, 1964 June (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - IBM, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - International Congress on Congenital Malformations (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - International Congress on Cybernetics and Systems (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - International Embryology Conference, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - International Embryology Conference, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - International Meeting of Neurobiologists (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - International Symposium on Physiology (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - IUBS 15th General Assembly (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Intracellular Transport, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Impromptu on Education (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Institute for Medical Research (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Istituto Superiore di Sanita (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Istituto Zoologia (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Italy, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Jahresversamonlung (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - James Ewing Society (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Kennaway Memorial Lectures (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Koln Lectures, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - L'archipel Scientifique (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - La Dynamique Globale des Systmes (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Lecture Book Index (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Lecture Book I, 1940-1944 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Lecture Book II, 1945-1950 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Lecture Book III, 1951-1954 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Lecture Book IV, 1955-1958 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Lecture Book V, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Lecture Book VI, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Lecture Book VI, 1961-1962 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Lecture Book VII, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Lecture Book VII, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Lecture Book VII, 1965-1966 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Lecture Book IX, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Lecture Book IX, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Lecture Book X, 1968-1970 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Lecture Book XI, 1971-1972 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Lecture Book XII, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Lecture Book XIII, 1975-1978 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Lectures and Conferences, 1955-1956 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Lectures and Conferences, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Lectures and Conferences, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Lenneberg Paper (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Lenneberg Symposium (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Litchfield, Oxford (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - London University College (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Lowell Lecture at Harvard (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Man-Centered Environmental Sciences (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Marshall Woods Series (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - MIT Lectures, 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - McCollum-Pratt Institute (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Medical University of South Carolina, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Mellon Lecture, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Molecular Specificity (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Morehouse College, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Mt. Sinai School of Medicine (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Munich-May, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - National Institutes of Health (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Neural Specificity (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Neurobiology (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Neurobiology Colloquium (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Neurobiology in Status Nascent (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow V (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Neuronal Dynamics and Axonal Flow VI (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Neuronal Organelles in Neuroplasmic Flow (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Neurosciences Research Program (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - New England Institute, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - New School of Social Research (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Academy of Medicine, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - New York University (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - IX International Congress of Pediatrics (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Holiday Lectures, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Holiday Lectures, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Holiday Science Writers' Seminar, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Holiday Science Series Lecture 1, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Holiday Science Series Lecture 2, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - 19th Annual Symposium on Cancer (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - North American Habitat Study Conferences (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - NATO Conference, Scotland, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina State University (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Notre Dame Honorary Degree (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Office of Naval Research (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Ohio State, 1962 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Olfactory (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - On Science as a Guide..... (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Order and Disorder (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Oxford, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Science Center Meeting (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Padua, Italy (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Panta Rhei (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Paris, 1973 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Perm State (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Physiology Laboratory, Cambridge (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Pirquet Society, 1963 November (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Pisa, Italy, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Pratt Institute (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Princeton, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Princeton Sigma XI (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Problems in the Development of Organisms (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Program Directors' Meeting, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Program in Cell Differentiation (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Psychology of Development, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Ravdin Lecture (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Rensselear Polytechnic, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - RI (Rockefeller Institute) Christmas Lecture, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - RI Colloquium, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - RU Research Colloquium, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - RI, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - RI Seminar (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Rogosin Laboratory Seminar (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Second International Biophysics Congress (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Second International Symposium for Cellular Chemistry, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Second International Symposium on Cytopharmacology (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Sigma XI, Brown University (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Sigma XI Installation (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Sixth International Embryological Conference, Helsinki, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Sorbonne Lecture, France (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Stevenson Memorial Lecture, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Study Program in Biophysical Science (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Stuttgart-Hohenheim, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Sweden, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Symposium of Growth Society, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Symposium on Control of Cellular Growth (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Symposium on Electron Microscopy (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Symposium on Hydrobiology (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Systems Character of All Nature (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Tallahassee (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Teachers College Seminar (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Teratology Society, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Texas A, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Texas Lectures, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Texas University Graduate Symposium (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Third Annual Symposium (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Third Conference on Cellular Dynamics (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Tissue Culture (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Tissue Culture Course (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Torch Club (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Trends in Neurophysiology (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Tbingen, 1975 February (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Tulane University, 1966 March (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Universit Libre de Bruxelles (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - US Department of Agriculture (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Unity of Science Symposium (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - University Menendez y Relayo Santander, Spain (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - University Center, Virginia, 1973 November (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - University of California - Irvine (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - University of California - Los Angeles (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - University of California - Los Angeles, 1964 September (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - University of California School of Medicine, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago-March, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - University of Giessen (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - University of Iowa (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - University of Maryland (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - University of Maryland Medical School (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - University of Miami (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - University of Michigan Symposium, 1960 March (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - University of Oregon, 1966 November (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - University of Rhode Island, 1962 October (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - University of Tel Aviv, 1963 November (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - University of Texas, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - University of Texas, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - University of Texas, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - University of Texas Convocation, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - University of Texas-Austin, 1966 April (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - University of Texas-Southwestern Medical School, 1964 April (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Van-Swieten Lecture (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Vesale Centenary, 1964 October (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Vienna, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Vienna, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Vienna, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Vienna Symposium, 1970 September (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Wainwright House, 1960 October (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Waldemar Summer Lecture, 1962 July (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Walter Reed Army Institute of Research (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Warwick Research Center (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Welch Foundation, 1961 December (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Wechsler Lecture (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Wellesley Lecture, 1967 February (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Western Reserve University, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Western Reserve University, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Western Reserve University Summer Institute (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - White House Conference on International Cooperation, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Wiener Volksbildung, 1971 May (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Wiesbaden, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Woods Hole Lecture (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Wound Healing Symposium, 1963 December (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Yale, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Yugoslavia, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Zoology Club (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Zuricher Forum, 1971 August (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Zurich Symposium, 1962 September (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Administrative Files, 1960-1971; 6; 1.76 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes primarily RU laboratory budget accounts and some grant budget information.
  - Account Summary, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Budget Account #22. 02 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Budget Account #22. 02 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Budget Account #22. 02 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Budget Account #22. 02 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Budget Account #22. 02 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Budget Account #22. 02 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Budget Account #22. 11 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Budget Account #22. 11 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Budget Account #22. 11 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Budget Account #22. 11 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Budget Account #22. 11 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Budget Account #22. 2701 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Budget Accounts, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Budget Accounts, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Faith Fund Account #1950 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Grant #7R01-CA-10096 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Grant #7R01-CA-10096 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Grant #7R01-CA-10096 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - NIH Grants (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - NIH Grants (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Old Annual Reports (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - RU (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - RU (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - RU (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - RU (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - RU (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Manuscripts, 1940-1971; 7; 3.96 Cubic Feet Extent is approximate.
  Includes notes, rough drafts and correspondence.
  Arranged in alphabetical order by title.
  - Aging (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - A Banded Structure on the Connective Tissue of the Nerve (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - A Basic Predecessor of Applied Heart Transplantation (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Bibliographies (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Biography (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Biomedical Excursions (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Bionde, Robert J. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Bringing the Public to Science (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Can Science Help to Thin the Fog....... (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Cardinal Sins in Biology (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Causality (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Cell Contact (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - The Challenge of Biology (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Chloraphenical vs. Conrol (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Convection and the Fate of Mitochondria in Nerve Fibers (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Deterioration in Cells (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Differentiation and Its Three Facets (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Dynamics and Mechanics of Neuroplasmic Flow (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Dynamics of Development (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Dynamics of the Membrane (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Ecology of Cells (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Electron Micrographs (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Electromyographic Studies on Normal and Pathological..... (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Electronmicroscopic Investigations on Axonal Flow (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Electronmicroscopic Investigations on Axonal Flow (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Erziehung fr Forschrift (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Experimentally Enforced Axonal Flow (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Final Report on Nerve Regeneration (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Foreword from Biology (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - From Cell Dynamics and Tissue Architecture (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Galley pages (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Genetic Neurology (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Grover, Norman B. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Growth Control Symposium (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Helical Arrays (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Hierarchical Systems (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Hierarchical Systems (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Journal of Ultrastructure Research (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - The Knowledge Explosion (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Life and Life Sciences (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Life as Seen from the Life Sciences (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Life as Seen from the Life Sciences (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Life on Earth (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Life, Order and Understanding (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Living Nature and the Knowledge Gap (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - The Living Nervous System (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - The Living System (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - The Living System (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Lyser, Katherine (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Mailing lists (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Manuscripts I (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Manuscripts II (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Manuscripts III (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Manuscripts IV (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - McAlear, James H. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Mechanism of Movements (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Message of Science (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Metanephros of Chicken Embryos (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Modern Biology Series (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Molecular Specificity (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Motility in Mature Nerve Fibers (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - National Policy for the Environment (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Nerve Fiber as a System (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Nerve Growth (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Nerve manuscripts (Box 76, Folder 4)